[{"answer": "That's all I do this for.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "How important is the award process to you?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "That is what talks in Washington, isn't it?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Well, that's right.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "Until they do, I don't think this goes anywhere, does it?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "Is this all good for him or is all the attention being lavish on Herman Cain good for Cain?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "You know, if there is one thing that I've learned that you can do is you can never predict for sure.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Michael Sitrick, I mean, could you imagine despite all this someone like Herman Cain winning now the Republican nomination and potentially becoming president?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "I think one of the things that may be appealing is his style, is the fact that he is the nonpolitician politician.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Would you say to him you got to get serious now or continue to ride the storm the way that he's doing?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Well, seven and a half hours of work today, Piers.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's more a focus for me on how many of those jurors have actually been jurors before.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "How much of that kind of detail to you is in favor perhaps to Conrad Murray or against him?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "Well, it really does depend on one of two things.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "And so, if we were predicting a time that might come back, are we looking at Monday now, Ted, do you think?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "I mostly mean with the guitar unfortunately.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "You don't just mean with a guitar, do you, Brad?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "I guess so.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "You are a bit of a player, aren't you?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "I love it.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "Do you still enjoy it, or does it become this dusty treadmill?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "AISLEY: I think he mostly just thought that I would love it like he did.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "So, when he gave you that guitar, do you think he had this wild, crazy notion that one day his grandson Brad was going to be performing to millions of people?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "What do you make of what's going on with America right now, financially, sort of a battle for its soul for whatever the new American Dream is?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "I think that the key is that people still -- they still look to us.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "What do you think of it?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "Well, yes, I think because -- although, I believe that there are more than -- there's more than one way to skin a cat.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "I mean, isn't this a very important time for America, isn't it vital now that the right person wins the next election?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "I want to play you the clip of what you said about President Obama, which is quite interesting, when he became president.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "There's areas where that has to happen, to just draw these lines and say I'm this or I'm that, that's where we're getting into trouble, you know?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "Was that -- was there always going to be a slight end of the honeymoon, do you think?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Yes, definitely.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "I mean, that is a bit of a result isn't it, as they say?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "She's good with that.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "How does your wife feel about the fact that you keep co- hosting with Carrie Underwood?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "Well, we also just had a big hit.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "How many more times will you do it before doubts start to creep in of what's going on here?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "You've won how many CMAs there?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "It's all I do this for.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "How important is the award process to you?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "It's a great moment.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "I know, I know, wouldn't that be something?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "Of all time.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "Of all time?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "Unique ability to sound instantly identifiable.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "What made him special?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "Would you really?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "She's -- she can sing -- and the beauty of it is, she could sing anything she wanted.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "That good?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "Totally.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Which is great for the country music world, isn't it?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "Yes, I think so.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "I mean, is she revered now in the -- in that world?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "I think she is.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "ORGAN: For that kind of decision she took?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "Did he get to see how successful you've become?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "I'm keenly aware of the fact that CMA is -- that's our Oscars.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "What were you feeling as you -- as you got emotional there?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "Don't need any more.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "ORGAN: How many more do you want to snaffle?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "It's totally true.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "I was -- I was 20 years old.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "Where were you watching the movie?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "Still pretty much surreal.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "And now 15 million albums later, can you believe it?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "Hum.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "We've never actually had our dinner date, have we?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "I think oh, my God, what a platt (ph).", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "I still get a fight.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "I mean, I love watching that because apart from the fact you seem so relaxed, the fact that you are just cavorting with one of the most famous television stars of all time, again, you must feel like pinching yourself, don't you?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "Every artist does have that wee bit of let's be the best.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Do you ever ask how you're going?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "It's the name of the game.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "ORGAN: So you've now gotten a little bit more now competitive?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "He is lovable.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "Quite adoptable, isn't he?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "That was a bit of a tricky one.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "What would your mother have made of this, do you think?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "Christian values, how to put yourself in other people's shoes and how to give your best even when things are really tough.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "What were the values she taught you?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "A bit pleased.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "And in that moment you must have felt I don't know -- how did you feel?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "It's a happy ending.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "Some of them have.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "They've contacted you and they said sorry?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "It is, yeah.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "Stuff of dreams isn't it?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "It does a bit.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "Does it still feel like that?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "I think I would have to say meeting Donny Osmond.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "What has been your biggest pinch me moment of them all?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "I certainly have, yes.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "You have a big soft spot for him, haven't you?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "Not yet.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "Have you sang with Donny yet?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "That was extra special.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "You sang for the Pope?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "Maybe 500,000.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "Have you any idea?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "OYLE: I believe in being a normal person.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "You could afford to live here in Hollywood in some huge mansion, but that doesn't interest you, does it?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "Ambitious to be continuing doing what I'm doing, continue to make people happy.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "What's the next ambition for you?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "It's from the album.", "docId": "111104pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "Of the singing variety, right?", "qSentId": 677}]